Tokimeki Balameter, JOSHOWN TV!
Yes, I know, it seems like a nostalgic arrangement, but...
What is it today?
Today is what you've all been waiting for!
Today is the "Kanamin UO Decision Game 2023!
We are waiting for you!
We've been waiting for you!
I'd like to provide you with the latest information on Kanamin, and moreover, I'd like to share with you the latest news on Kanamin.
And moreover, since it's been a year since the last Kanamin bath, we thought that you might be able to use it too.
We wanted to try it as soon as possible, didn't we?
Yes, we were already anxious.
Good, then it was the perfect project for us.
I made it the first one.
I thought that there would be a lot of easy-to-understand questions.
I'm really under a lot of pressure.
Good luck with the first one!
By the way, last time, Pio-chan was Kanamin UO.
I think I have no choice but to win again.
After all, you got 5 points here, didn't you?
That's great.
I got a lot of points, so this time I got 10 points for everything.
Ten points?
Yes, one point this time.
One butterfly.
Aiming for 10 Buto.
Ten.
That's hard to say.
10 buto.
Aim for 10 Butchou.
You are very strong, 10 chos.
Please think about it with everyone who is watching.
I'm counting on you.
Let's start with the first question.
What spice do you like the most?
Eeeee!
This is difficult.
What spice do you like the most?
You mean spicy spices, right?
That's right.
Ah! I think I might have figured it out.
I often say that.
I'm not sure about the kanji.
It's difficult to understand this one in Kanji.
Difficult? Kanji.
That's what you said. Kanami told me.
But there's quite a variety.
What? What did she say?
Favorite spice?
My favorite.
It's hard to say which spice I like the best.
Is there a time limit on this? This time.
Forever.
Quick, quick, quick.
30 seconds.
Maybe.
Fastest?
This is the one I like the most.
I'm probably saying it a lot, aren't I?
I think I have.
I also put it in stories and stuff.
Stories?
But maybe this one.
I've got the o-hara.
That's great.
Maybe it's the right answer.
I've already come up with the bara.
What? It's no good.
That's the end of it.
I don't know if it's spice or not. I don't know if it's spice or not.
I wrote it down.
Only one came up.
That's saying a lot, isn't it?
I think I'm done.
Then, let's all start at once, please.
Let's start with Julia.
Gochujang.
Yuzu kosho.
Owa-ja-o.
Owa-ja-o?
Ichimin.
Ichimin?
It's moving. I'm moving.
Just because you don't know.
I'll disqualify you.
By the way, is there a spy named Ichimin?
No, Ichimin.
What's that?
When I had Kanami, Ichimin became Ichimin.
Then, I can give 100% as "love".
If you do it again.
If I do it again, I might be disqualified.
I don't know.
So that's how it is.
What is yukkejang?
Yugkejang? Spijujang?
Gochujang?
Isn't it gochujang?
I think it's gochujang.
I think it's gochujang.I think it's gochujang.
It's not much.
Is it?
It's a cute pronunciation.
I love Korean food.
I thought it was gochujang.
Okay, everyone, let's see the correct answer.
Please.
Cute.
What's the spice that Aimon likes best?
Huajiao.
Yay!
I love the aroma.
Yes, so here is my favorite.
Huajiao.
No, no, no.
Answer.
Next.
That was definitely wrong.
It's huajiao.
I didn't recognize the taste.
It's a little difficult to write.
So, the correct answer is Oharu.
That's great.
I felt like I was saying it a lot.
I often find it in Chinese dishes such as tantanmen.
The hoisinjiao was in the tantanmen Hito-chan gave me.
It was really delicious.
I often find it in Chinese food such as wan pudding.
I'm writing this because it's difficult. Because it's difficult.
I didn't know that.
It's really delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
They sell kaki no tane (persimmon seed) from Huajiao.
What? Kaki no tane?
Yes, they are.
They are really tasty. I recommend them because they are not too spicy and they are really tasty.
It smells so good.
It was recommended to me.
Yes, I did.
It's difficult, but it hit the spot.
It's difficult.
Next.
I saw it earlier.
This way.
The second question. Which part of your face do you often receive compliments from makeup artists?
Ehhhh! I've never seen it.
It's a part.
You mean it's not skin or something?
Parts.
By parts, do you mean eyebrows, eyes, mouth, nose, etc.?
You mean V.
By parts, do you mean skin is not included?
It's the part you make up when you do makeup.
Oh, I see.
Are there any parts you don't do?
Not the ears.
I'll do makeup for 30 seconds.
Okay, now let me ask you to think about it.
I've heard that you can draw any part you want.
Aki-chan said, "Just draw whatever you want.
You can draw whatever you want.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Are you really drawing?
How does it look like?
What does it look like? I don't know.
I probably wouldn't know.
It's quite likely that it's not the same person who always does my makeup, but a new makeup artist.
Aaah! Wait! I might have figured it out!
Time is up, right?
Yes, I'm out of time.
All right, everyone.
Now, please all give your answers at once.
Let's go!
Let's start with Julia.
Skin. Eyelashes. Nose.
Nose.
Pio looks confident.
Because her nose is so beautiful.
It's so beautiful. It's true.
What? No?
No? No?
No?
It was my eyelashes.
I'm sorry.
Hanami.
Besides, isn't your handwriting wrong?
What?
These guys.
The characters are different.
It's backwards. Like this.
Like this. Like this.
What's with that face?
It's a character.
A new character has appeared.
You can read it, right?
You can read it.
So I understand.
I was looking at it too much and didn't notice it for a moment.I was looking too much and didn't notice for a moment.
Please give me the correct answer.
Which facial part does Kanami often receive compliments from makeup artists?
Wow, where is it?
Oh, Matsuri is
Lips.
Ew.
Lips are good, too, right?
No, they're all good.
I'm so confused.
They're all so good.
They're all good.
I'm torn between the lips, too.
I'm lost.
Hirano Mama said...
Sarabi's lips are good.
You know, in the dark.
If only the lips are raised...
I wonder if it's okay to look at it.
They were raised.
Her lips...
I never liked my lips.
I don't know, it's kind of annoying, and I get compliments on it, so...
I'm getting more and more compliments on them, so... Oh, I don't know.
They're a little pouty.
But, I mean, isn't that a little unfair?
I mean, you have great eyebrows.
And your eyelashes. And your eyes.
Aren't they all right?
Yes, they are.
But...
Ms. Hirano.
Yes, you are correct.
Your lips.
The third question is here.
Uhhh...
The size of Kanomi's head.
So, let's see what you think.
What, here?
How big is the head?
How do they measure it?
50, 40...
How big is your head?
I measured it with a tape measure, and it's here.
What is the size of a normal human head?
I don't know.
Oh, is this the closest
closest to you?
His head is perfect.
Oh, but...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's the first dot.
What? What's the first dot?
I'm screwed.
That means it's the right answer.
Whoever was closest was right.
Not the closest one.
Dot what? Nazi.
Uh-oh.
Ten million more.
Oh, I see.
Oh!
May I?
Yes, it's good.
Then, everyone, please give us your answers.
Go ahead.
What?
Wait, 38,000 is impossible.
Sixty.
38,000?
488,000.
48,000.
Oh, wait. What is it?
I'm totally different from the others.
33,000.
Not 60?
It's smaller.
I thought it was smaller.
It's difficult.
Please give me the correct answer.
What is the size of your head, Kanami?
Her head size is
52.4 cm.
This is the size.
It's about this size.
Yes, my head size was 42.4cm.
Why did I say it was so difficult?
Why is it so difficult?
There is more for everyone, so please hang in there.
For now, we still have to finish.
I got one minute longer.
This is your lucky problem.
We've got a lucky problem.
Let's go.
Let's do it!
Yes! What are Hanane's recent feelings?
Isn't it that one already?
It's a lucky question!
Think about it!
Is it not this one? Maybe.Isn't this it? Maybe.
What?
What, this isn't it?
What are you doing?
Oh, no?
No?
I don't know. I didn't see it.
Oh, this isn't it?
Healing?
Healing. Healing.
Oh, my God, the countdown has started.
Wait!
Fourteen seconds.
I have no idea.
It's okay, right?
Oh, it's just a day.
Hiyori.
I made a mistake.
How many seconds?
Oh, wait, I made a mistake.
Oh, this is it.
I believe that's the word.
Maybe.
I'm probably with you.
It's either that way or that way.
I hope that's okay.
Okay, then.
Wait for the correct answer, ladies and gentlemen.
Okay.
Ah!
What?
Beef tongue.
Ahhh...
Makeup.
Fixing it
I wondered which one it was.
Oh, makeup.
It's not makeup?
Isn't this soil?
It's not Cogynew?
It's Cogginew.
It's not cogginew?
It's true that both are Kanami's favorites.
I saw the flowers in Drogo's book.
Beef tongue to heal you!
Beef tongue heals you, right?
Eat it.
It'll heal you.
It's definitely Make-chan!
Let's see the correct answer.
This way, please.
What is Kanami's recent healing?
Yes, my recent healing is...
On YouTube.
I watch videos of Cogimune singing on YouTube
on YouTube.
My favorite is "Hatsukoi Cider".
Give it a listen.
Wow!
Oh my God!
Yay!
You have a great voice.
I thought it was makeup.
That's amazing.
Cogimune.
I'm trying to watch a video of Cogimune singing.
Watching Cogimyun's videos.
First Love Cider
You have prawns, right?
The shrimp...
She's doing the coggy-mune call.
He's so cute!
Cogimyun!
Cogimyun.
It's super cute.
Look at that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Identity book.
Identity book. Oh, my God.
What do we do now? We're all going to be punished, except for the rest of us.
This way, please.
How old is Hanane's skin measured in 2022?
Ehhhh...
Why did you measure it?
You know, those things you see at hot springs?
I know, right?
You know, the ones that come out when you tap your skin?
It depends on what it is.
I've measured mine.
I'm gonna get fat.
Fat.
15... 17, 8?
Oh, my God.
That's great, that's great, that's great.
Okay, thinking time.
Here we go.
But you're even younger.But you're much younger.
Sure looks a lot younger.
Ah, 2022.
Today.
Well, I don't know.
For the first time in my life.
You chewed this.
Yup.
Okay.
Yes, this one fits, too, right?
This one fits, right?
OK.
Okay.
Let's hear your answers.
Ready.
Julien, 18.
Fifteen.
Seventeen.
Oh, Minatu5.
Eh?
Then let's have a quick look.
Huh?
What is your skin age measured in 2022?
Yes. My skin age is 23 now, and I measured it when I was 23.
My skin age was 20 years old.
Ehhhhh!
You don't see it.
It's so frustrating.
Ah, she's not here.
So it's 20.
It was 20.
Wow, that's close.
A little higher.
I feel a little awkward.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I feel like everyone can tell.
I don't like it.
But you know, it depends on the occasion.
Is that so?
Yes, yes, yes.
Wow, that's frustrating.
I thought you were out of line.
I thought it was a dead end.
This is bad.
Everyone.
Ehhhh, it's so hard.
I wonder how many I've done now?
Fifth.
Oh, there's only five left.
We're only halfway through.
But what are we going to do?
You can get back on track, even if you're a pussy. I'm down to two points.
Oh no.
Well, everyone, please hang in there.
Here's the next question.
Wow!
Kanabibu's herb is beef tongue.
How many times have you eaten beef tongue in 2023?
At this point in time.
How many times have you eaten it?
Yes, so some people have a bit of an advantage in this.
There are people who have looked at the folder together.
I haven't seen it.
Only those who have seen it.
No, that's an advantage.
This is the only person.
It says on the picture where he ate.
What?
We were practicing earlier.
He mentioned it before.
It looks really delicious.
Yes, as of now.
At the moment.
Okay, then.
Yes, sinking start.
Wow, I don't think I'm going to go that far.
I ate a lot of food last year.
I didn't take pictures of it all.
How much?
I kind of wished I had made a collection of them all, so I made it public.
So this time I took pictures of everything.
Oh, they are so nice.
Did you have these for Valentine's Day?
It's only been a month and a half at this point, right?
That's right.
That's, um...
Bento?
There's bento?
Then maybe more.
But we only ate lunch together once.
That's right.
I thought it was delicious.
That was my first time this year.
Then once for everyone.
That's about it.
Maybe that's too much.
Definitely too much.
But I guess it's time to call it a sing-along.But I'll just say that Singing Time is over now.
Ladies and gentlemen, let me be the one to give you the answer.
Let's make it fit.
Yes, please.
Please.
Four times.
Ten.
Three.
Four times.
Five.
What?
This is something about my...
No way.
Huh?
A little bit.
They're all different.
Let's take a look.
Please.
Kanami's favorite food is beef tongue. How many times have you eaten beef tongue in 2023?
Yes, I have eaten beef tongue 6 times this year!
Wow!
That's a lot of food!
That was close!
It's the first time!
Hey, I should have increased the number.
What a shame!
So I ate beef tongue 6 times in the year 2023!
Wow, so frustrating!
Oh no!
I thought Kanamin and I had gotten closer over the past year.
Seems like we've grown apart a bit.
We've grown apart.
Everyone said it was a lucky problem.
That's what they said.
I wasn't lucky at all.
It's really a lucky problem.
You write in Kana-chan's blog every time.
What is the first greeting for both of you?
I've been doing this ever since I started blogging.
For years.
Yes, we are singers like female nerves, ladies and gentlemen.
Everyone is moving fast on the fences. Except Julia.
Julia, she said she was looking at my blog.
I'm thinking about it, and I'm picturing the last greeting on Radio Japan.
Tokimitsu Smile, at the beginning, every time I jibbled.
What? Huh?
And the parent too?
I don't know.
No, maybe it's not.
Maybe it's definitely different.
I don't know, maybe I'm different.
Why don't you remember?
What? Kanji.
What? This one?
Okay, is everyone all right?
Yes, is it okay?
Well, no, no, no, no, definitely not.
Please, give me an answer.
I'm Tsubajinobiri.
From Chiria, it's been a while since I've had a chance to talk to you.
Take it easy on the road.
I was a lazy cat, taking it easy on the road.
I'm in no hurry, it's been a lazy day for me.
Today, too, it was a lazy day at the tsunamis.
Oh, I see.
Then, please do me a favor.
What is the closing speech that Kanamin writes in every blog?
Yes, I do. If you have been following my blog, you would surely understand.
It's the last greeting that I have been writing for about 5, 6, 7 years now.
Here I go.
I'll see you all soon.
That was Kanamin.
I'm Kanamin.
It doesn't include the word "while".
Then, then...
I'm definitely not good at this.
It's written only for the year.
Yes. Then, let's not be in a hurry and write only in the year. I'm Kanamin. That would be the correct answer.
But it's also okay without it.
Yes.
It's okay.
Yay!
That's why
I was a nervous kanamimin.
It's a correct answer!
Yes!
Correct!
Today, too!
Today!
No rush, no worries!
I usually do this at night.
At night, too, today, no rush, relaxing on azaleas!
This is the last stage.
Now...
Oharu has 3 points and Aki-chan has 1 point.
OLA!
Are you okay, everyone?
Oh no.Oh no.
I'm falling all over the place.
Three more questions to go.
This is bad.
I didn't think I could answer this many.
I thought everyone could answer more.
Sorry.
Simple Society
Thank you.
Good luck.
Hang in there.
My hands are shaking.
What's the most exciting dinner you have when you get home from work?
The most exciting dinner is the one I have when I get home.
So on the other hand, it's not my favorite thing to eat.
But it's something I like to eat at home.
But I really eat this all the time.
You like it? You love it?
Is that what you're saying? Likes it.
What? I didn't say that.
I think she's saying... what? You haven't?
I'm too familiar with it. I haven't said it.
I eat it all the time.
Thinking time is starting.
What? I know it's Scalby's favorite food.
Do you think he'll eat it when he gets home at night?
Uh, what? No?
No?
I'll eat it when I get home tonight.
This isn't it?
You eat a lot.
I'm glad.
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy.
I'd be happy with that.
That much?
That's not it?
No?
That one?
I like it as much as I like beef tongue.
What?
That's not so bad.
All right, everyone, let's hear your answers.
Go on, go on, go on!
Hot pot.
Hot pot
Ramen noodles!
Hot pot, hot pot, hot pot. We're eating hot pot, aren't we?
I remember you saying nabe, nabe, nabe.
But I like them all.
I like...
That's right.
But here's the one I'm most excited about.
What's the most exciting thing you have for dinner when you get home from work?
Laughing.
I get excited when I come home and have this.
It's a negitoro maki.
I've never heard of it. Never heard of it.
Wait a minute, everyone.
I think we should talk.
But wait.
You all need to hear this at my house.
It's really messed up.
No, it's Mr. Come and Leave.
I'm, you know, I've never been reported at all.
It's Legitolo!
Then you've never come.
You used to say hot pot.
Hot pot is healthy, so I don't like to eat it.
Eh?
When we go out to eat sushi or seafood together, I always eat leggitro.
What do you think, everyone?
Let's go next time.
Next time, I'm going to eat leggitro.
See you next time!
Kanamin
What is the name of the brand you produce?
What? I know.
This is for you guys.
English.
I can't! Ehhhh!
What? Seriously, I can't.
No.
I'm fine either way.
I'm sure you'll get all the names that don't come up.
I think we all know exactly what it is.
I think this is it.
Definitely not.
What? I don't know if I know English.
Help! I don't know!
Oh, no! I'm done!
Oh, wait, the English scale.
Oh, God, I'm so stupid.
Oh, no, wasn't there a Contown in there?
What should I do?
Oh, wait.Eh, wait.
I saw your Instagram too.
I'm looking at it too.
I also look at the clothes and stuff.
I know the logo.
I did the online event.
I know.
Pillon. I messed up.
Okay, everyone.
I'm counting on you.
Just a minute.
Charmy Rose.
I don't know.
It's Rose, somehow.
I didn't know because I wanted a rose.
Charme Rose.
Callum.
What's in it?
Callum?
Is there a rose in it?
Calum.
Where does it come from?
What's Carnum?
It's not another brand, is it?
You shouldn't write other people's brands.
There are similar brand names.
What's Carnum?
Don't write other people's brands.
I think it fits.
Carnum.
I think it's easy to understand Rose.
It might be spelled differently.
Rose.
Please give me the correct answer.
Sanami, what is the name of the brand you produce?
Yes.
I think this one is a recent memory.
I'm sure you all have a recent memory.
I'm sure you can guess.
Aaaaah!
Wait!
I think I got it right.
Why not?
Rose.
Is it right?
Yes, so here it is.
Charme Rose.
Did you guys really get it right?
It's a little reflection on my butt.
Yes, so the correct answer is Oharu.
Yes!
I got it right!
That's great!
Yes!
I got it all right!
That's great!
Yes, the correct answer is Oharu.
There, there, there, there!
It's wine or eeka.
Charmeuse on the butt.
Charmeuse. It's cute.
Yes!
That's great. You even know how to spell it.
That's great!
I didn't think the spelling was right.
Yay!
Four points.
Four?
Yay! I'm so happy!
I got about half of them right.
I did it!
One more question to go.
Oh no.
One more question.
Now, Haa-chan has 4 points and Aki-chan has 1 point.
The last problem is not a problem at all, as long as you get maximum 3 points.
Aki-chan tied for first place?
Aki-chan could be in first place in total percentage.
This is, you know, what I have already told you to look at.
Once.
Then, let's go.
Next time, Aki-chan could be 1 point and Aki-chan could be 1 point.
Yes, last issue. What is the hobby that Kanamin said she would like to start in the last Kanamin Method?
Yes, so
She said it in the Kanamin Method one year ago.
Two years ago?
That's the first time she mentioned it. It was the first time I mentioned it.
There are three in total.
Did it really start?
I don't know about that. I don't know.We don't know that. I don't know.
Eh~... Is it cutamine?
But not if it's wrong.
It's good if it's just one. It's okay if it's just one.
Isn't it this one? It's a mistake.
But you're writing the wrong one?
Because it's wrong. If there's one of them, that's one point.
Really? Three, three.
Then why don't you just write a lot? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that's it. I'm writing up to three.
Oh, you don't mind? Up to three.
One more. I'll have to think of three more.
It's a bit long.
Hobbies?
Hobbies I'd like to start.
What are you going to do?
Nothing comes to mind.
I'm sure I did.
I might be doing it.
Nothing's coming to mind over there.
Okay, everybody.
It's about time.
Please.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Yes, so please open everyone's answers.
Also, from Julia.
Let's call it live time.
Creré.
You know, like nutritional balance, dietary balance.
Eating habits.
Yeah. Growing employee muscats.
I grow them.
Scuba diving, beef tongue tours, and the arch.
You're going to the arch?
Something with a bow.
Baking cookies, camping alone, driving.
Sounds like my kind of thing.
It's full of them.
Driving, camping alone, eh.
What?
I'm eating, a lot.
Okay, everyone.
Did I mention camping alone?
I didn't.
Well, let's see your answer. Here it is.
What is the hobby that Kanani mentioned in the last interview that she would like to start?
Yes, I have three hobbies. There are three. One is fishing, one is camping alone, and one is scuba diving.
If you guessed at least one of them, you get 1 point. If you got three right, you get three points.
Were you right?
Yes, I did. So, if the correct answers are fishing, scuba diving, and camping alone, then
The first correct answer is Oharu's scuba diving.
Aki-chan's correct answer is to camp alone.
HIRO's camping by himself is the correct answer.
But Junya's camp is also correct.
Junya's camp is also correct.
Wait a minute! No way!
No way!
Wait! Could it be that only one of them has 0 points?
So, here are the results.
Junya and Kyurin got 1 point.
Aki-chan with 2 points. And the winner, Oharu with 5 points.
Yay!
And the resumption was Hitoka.
But you know, this is just like that one year old YouTube...
I saw you doing it.
Is this Haru-chan's too?
Yes, I did it last year.
I'm so happy.
You're kidding.
No, it's not.
I wonder if there's a penalty for this.
You're writing something.
I don't like it.
Cogimun.
Confess to KANAMIN like a cogimun.
Confessing at close range.
Even if you don't understand Cogimun, just imagine.
But why don't you ask KANAMIN to show you the song he sang?
A cat?
A cat sang.
Yes! Kogimun!
I'm so nervous!
I'm usually the one who gets nervous.
What should I do? Help me!
I'm scared!
Kogihomi-un is being punished.
Kogimyun...
What's he talking about?
Garbage?
Oh, and finally, a "Jun"...
What are you doing?
Okay, here we go.
Ahhh...
It hasn't started yet.
Not yet, Gomi-chan.
I can totally see you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm not moving.
We've been looking at each other forever.
Here we go.Yes, here we go.
Here we go.
Hito-chan's impersonation of Kogimyu. Confession.
I love you, Jun.
So cute!
What's being shown?
He's putting it in the mirror.
Is it over?
What are they showing you?
It's embarrassing.
What's on it?
What did you think?
It was cute.
Oh, my God.
This store is the only big one.
It's my idea of a convenience store.
Let's go camping together.
I didn't want to be here.
I'm pretty sure I made a mistake.
Looks like they're going somewhere.
I don't know.
Do it this way.
Is he okay? Is he alive?
I'm frozen. I can't breathe.
Calamine's taking the punishment.
Surprisingly, the fire is going strong.
Calamine wins!
How did everyone like it?
It's funny.
It was frustrating.
Next time we play, I'll aim for 10 points.
I'll do my best.
Please aim for the championship!
That's all I have to say.
Tea?
Good morning, sir.
Yay!
So, Yukari.
It's great that J is going!
Yay!
I've been waiting for this.
For this.
It's the overwhelming winner.
We did it!
Yes, thank you all for watching.
See you next week.
Subscribe to our channel!
Yes! If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel...
Subscribe to our channel...
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Are you serious?
Are you sure?
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'll be waiting for you!
I'll be waiting!
I'm waiting for your comments!
Thank you for watching!